<resources>
    <string name="app_name">demo-paint</string>

    <string name="button_library_video">Paint</string>

    <string name="demo_message">This app demonstrates an example of our custom paint for Android.</string>
    <string name="demo_message_contact_us">You like it? Contact us <a href="https://www.facebook.com/mobiledevpro/">#MobileDevPro</a></string>
    <string name="app_title_set_signature">Paint</string>

    <string name="text_form">
        I grant to @companyName ("Company") and Company\'s assigns, licensees and
        successors, with respect to video/film/photographic/digital images and audio recordings
        taken of me, the right to use my image/likeness and/or name in all forms and media
        including composite or modified representations for all purposes, including publicity,
        advertising, trade or any commercial purpose throughout the world and in perpetuity.
        I waive the right to inspect or approve versions of my image used for publication or
        the written copy that may used in connection with the images. I also give my full and
        complete permission, without compensation or limitation to the Company to take, record,
        publish, display or obtain testimonials or other statements from me in any media, by any means,
        methods including, but not limited to,advertising, marketing and promotional materials.
        I understand and agree that the Statements may be used, reproduced, re-used, altered,
        modified, edited or changed with or without identifying me and my affiliation. I hereby release
        and discharge the Company from any and all claims, and demands arising out of or in
        connection with the use of above-referenced images and/or audio recordings. This authorization
        and release shall also ensure to the benefit of the legal representatives, advertising agencies,
        media outlets, subcontractors, licensees, assigns and nominees of the Company. I further
        relinquish all rights to use any of the above-referenced images or audio recordings for my
        own purposes.
        \n\nI have read and understood this agreement and I am over the age of 18.
        \n\nI have the legal right to consent to and do consent to the terms and conditions of this release.
    </string>

</resources>
